yello.in 2011-12-31

# India Classifieds Free for Cars, Real Estate, Job » Yello.in

|   
  
| 

## Privacy Policy  
  
---  
**1\. Information collection and use**  
| 1.1 | If you wish to use this site you must ensure that your personal information (as applicable to the sale) is complete and accurate. This personal information includes your email address and, if necessary your name, address, postal code and payment information. You also guarantee that you are legally competent to use this site.  
---|---  
  |    
1.2 | Your personal information will be used only to complete a sale with an interested buyer.   
  |    
1.3 | Yello collects the necessary details to make improvements to the site using IP information and cookies. This information is used to improve user friendliness.   
  |    
1.4 | Yello believes in doing all it can to protect the privacy of its users. Personal information is not used to improve our services to the users of Yello. Personal information is not made available to a third party without the user's explicit permission.   
  |    
1.5 | You give Yello permission to provide information to legal authorities if it is necessary according to their judgment   
  |    
1.6 | Yello may contain links to other sites (by means of a hyperlink, banner or button). While visiting another site, you are subject to the privacy rules and regulations of the site you are visiting. You acknowledge that Yello has not developed these sites and therefore has no influence on, and takes no responsibility for, the content of these sites.  
  |    
1.7 | If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, Yello will ask you for your friend's name and email address. Yello will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. Yello stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. Your friend may contact us at [tcg.classifieds@gmail.com](mailto:tcg.classifieds@gmail.com) to request that we remove this information from our database.   
  |    
1.8 | From time-to-time Yello may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our site. If you participate, Yello will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and email address and demographic information (such as zip code). 

Yello use this information to notify contest winners and award prizes, to monitor site traffic or personalize the site (in the case of anonymous information collected in surveys), to send participants an email newsletter.   
  
  |    
1.9 | If you purchase a service from us, Yello request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, and address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). 

Yello use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you.   
  
  |    
1.10 | We do not share your profile with other third parties.   
  |    
1.11 | If you do not agree to be bound by the above articles, we strongly advise you NOT to use Yello  
   
**2\. Communications from the Site**  
| 2.1 | Yello will occasionally send you information on products, services, special deals, promotions. You can sign up for these emails from us on our registration page.   
Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option not to receive these types of communications. Please see the "Choice and Opt-out."   
---|---  
  |    
2.2 | If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), Yello will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to unsubscribe. Please see the "Choice and Opt-out" section.   
  |    
2.3 | Yello will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, Yello might send you an email.   
Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account. You may opt-out of these communications. Please see "Choice and Opt-out."   
  |    
2.4 | Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, Yello will send you a welcoming email to verify your username and password. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. Yello will communicate with you by email or telephone, in accordance with your wishes.   
   
**3.3. Information Sharing and Disclosure**  
| 3.1 | Yello share aggregated demographic information about our user base with our partners and advertisers. This information does not identify individual users.  
Yello do not link aggregate user data with personally identifiable information.   
---|---  
  |    
3.2 | Yello DO NOT Share Personally Identifiable Information with Third Parties.  
  |    
3.3 | Yello reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.  
   
**4\. Choice/Opt-out**  
| 4.1 |  Yello provides you the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes, when we ask for this information. For example, if you purchase a product/service but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us, you can indicate your preference on our order form.   
---|---  
  |    
  | If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing us at [tcg.classifieds@gmail.com](mailto:tcg.classifieds@gmail.com).   
  |    
  | You will be notified when your personal information is collected by any third party that is not our agent/service provider, so you can make an informed choice as to whether or not to share your information with that party.   
   
**5\. Log Files**  
| As is true of most Web sites, Yello gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.   
---  
   
We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information. IP addresses are tied to personally identifiable information for security purposes of our users.   
   
**6\. Cookies**  
| A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. Yello uses cookies on this site. Yello does not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site Yello use session ID cookies and persistent cookies. Yello use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's "help" file. To learn more about how to mange cookies, please click here.  
---  
   
Yello set a persistent cookie to store your passwords, so you don't have to enter it more than once. Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.  
   
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site will be limited   
   
This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Yello only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.  
   
**7.Clear Gifs (Web Beacons)**  
| Yello employs and our thir d party advertising partner employs a software technology called clear gifs that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective and allow us to count users who have visited those pages. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user's computer harddrive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers' personally identifiable information.   
---  
   
To learn more about our advertising company's use of clear gifs, please go to <http://privacy2.msn.com/en-th/fullnotice.aspx#PERSONAL>  
   
We use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns. If you would like to opt-out of these emails, please see "Choice and Opt-out."   
   
**8.Third Party Advertisers**  
| The banner ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to users by us. We share Web site usage information about users with a reputable third party, for the purpose of targeting our Internet banner advertisements on this site.  
---  
   
For more information about our third-party advertiser, please click here   
   
**9\. Access to Personally Identifiable Information**  
  
If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by making the change on our member information page or by emailing our Customer Support at [tcg.classifieds@gmail.com](mailto:tcg.classifieds@gmail.com) or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below.  

**10\. Security**  
| The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).   
---  
   
We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.   
   
If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send email us at [tcg.classifieds@gmail.com](mailto:tcg.classifieds@gmail.com)  
   
**11\. Business Transitions**  
  
In the event Yello goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.  

**12.Changes in this Privacy Statement**  
|  If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.   
---  
   
We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.   
   
**13\. Contact Us**  
| If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: [tcg.classifieds@gmail.com](mailto:tcg.classifieds@gmail.com)  
---  
   
Yello Media Ltd.  
A 27 H, Sector 16  
Noida, Ghaziabad  
Uttar Pradesh 201 301  
tel +91 120 391 9862  
fax +91 120 305 2660
